TODO continue editing at 00:25:01
well this is dr. Stan here at Radio
Liberty coming differen the hills
overlooking beautiful and picturesque
Monterey Bay and bringing you the story
behind the story the news behind the
news hoping to convince you that reality
is usually scoffed at and allusion is
usually king but in the battle for
survival of Western civilization it's
going to be reality and not illusion or
delusion that's going to determine just
what the future will bring now I want to
introduce to you dr. Lawrence Dunnigan
and dr. Dunnigan is a pediatrician he
practice in Pittsburgh practices in the
eastern part of the United States and
he's been practicing in for 30 years but
some 28 years ago he heard a fascinating
lecture given by a dr. day who had been
a professor at the Medical School he had
attended and this talk was given to a
group of young doctors and with the
proviso that nobody would take notes and
nobody would record what was said dr.
day then went on to become a director of
the Planned Parenthood Federation so now
right now let's introduce dr. denigan
dr. Dunnigan so good for you to be where
they start to have you with us today
my pleasure all right fine well why
don't you just give our listeners the
background of this incredible incredible
story you heard 28 years ago which is so
prophetic as far as what's unfolding
today and let me just for the listener a
comment that one of the things that was
said 28 years ago was we would have sex
without reproduction and reproduction
without sex and as we begin thinking
about the artificial insemination and
now the new cloning process you realize
that what was said 28 years ago to a
young pediatrician is all coming to pass
today a part of a long-range plan of a
group of men who do have an agenda so
why don't you pick up the story from
there well when we sat down to listen to
the lecture we were all expecting
something clinical
dr. dey his areas of primary research
concern had always been newborn
premature birth and the problems with
kernicterus
coming from neonatal jaundice and
temperature control in premature babies
so what we were all expecting something
scientific and as the presentation
unfold it was quite a surprise because
there was nothing scientific it was all
of what we might call sociologic and as
you alluded a while ago dr. day and
indicated that he wanted to see nobody
taking notes or using a tape recorder
because the things he was going to talk
about actually he said in the process if
you ever quote me on these things I will
deny them he seemed to be indicating
that there could be some sort of
physical danger to him for speaking out
about such things that was for ace
suggests that I think rather than an
explicit statement but you know we hear
that sort of thing very early enough
what you're anticipating to be a
scientific presentation that really
caught my attention you know what are
you going to be telling us that could
put you in some danger one way or
another so anyway as the presentation
unfolded he began by stating that
anybody with an eighth grade education
could do the arithmetic and determine
that the earth would soon be
overpopulated if there were no limits
put on human reproduction and part pulse
of the overpopulation then would be
outgrowing our natural resources and
over pollution of the planet
these people always refer to the world
or the earth is the planet so in the
beginning it seemed as though
presentation was almost an apology for
things that we would in the audience
find unpalatable but there were several
times in presentation where he would say
this is the only way there's no other
way this is sort of implying that he
knew these things would maybe not sound
acceptable to many if not all in the
audience so the thing that he really
this whole thing hung on was population
control and up until that time I had
heard most of us had heard that term
population control to me it primarily
meant limiting births by the end of the
presentation I realized that population
control has a much much broader meaning
than just limiting number of births and
even who or who may not be allowed to
give birth because the presentation
covered just every human endeavor
education employment industry
entertainment sports toys for children
clothing a whole bunch of things that
maybe we can get into as week one hears
as time allows but mentioning as you did
six without reproduction and
reproduction without sex that was they
an important part of this also money in
banking which was toward the end of his
presentation the cashless society moved
from cash to credit cards to a single
credit card to a single identifying
court
and only had to end because cards can be
lost or stolen some sort of implant
under the skin in those days silicone
implants were under the very first
stages of development silicone is inert
so the body tends to tolerate it fairly
well in this implant them would serve as
identification and be an element in
carrying on Commerce which as I say
would replace cash replace Chuck's from
a checking account replace plastic
credit cards which back at that time
we're starting to really accelerate in
use so that all of these items that
serve your financial banking needs also
would serve for identification and this
could be implanted laughing because at
the time he said some of you hearing
this will right away think there is a
religious connotation here and at that
time I had no idea what he's referring
to I was not much of a Bible scholar and
then it was only later that I read the
book of the apocalypse about the the
market based on the hand to the forehead
and I made a connection then I realized
why he said what he says did he tell you
what the relationship was to banking and
international finance or was this just a
casual remark about the fact that we
would progress to a situation or society
where everybody would be marked and
identified yeah he went the presentation
was that
the changes that he was projecting from
then 1969 the target date to have them
all in place was the turn of the century
the 2000 right uh you ever take a few
years according to how well it would
progress but there was where they were
shooting and this was the worldwide not
just the United States or not just
United States Europe and you know
so-called Western civilization but this
was to be global the entire world now
did he tell you who was going to be
doing it or was it just it's going to
happen and and there's some group behind
this it's going to happen there he never
used a proper noun he used only one
proper down in the entire presentation
yeah and that it was the Rockefeller
Institute now what was the tie of the
Rockefeller Institute into this now did
he say that had to do with the research
and the treatment of cancer and there
was something about they had treatments
for cancer but they didn't want to
release them because we had to have
people dying off what was that yes
that's just about what it was that many
or most cancers now could be cured now
this is back in 1969 many are most
cancer is now or curable but the
information has been held in Rockefeller
Institute files because imagine what
would happen if people stopped dying of
cancer. - and of course that's exactly what
Thomas Malthus wrote about back in 1800
you know we had to have people dying so
we could have new people born. mm-hmm
fascinating. okay well just I pardon me
for interrupting you but I just wanted
to bring that fact out so this is 28
years ago you're hearing the predictions
of what the future holds for the world
so why don't you pick it up from there.
- well
I'm just trying to recall where he
started, there was this general overview
about controlling earth/birth, who may or may
not be allowed to have birth, implying
that certain people would be not allowed
to have children, most people would be
allowed to exceptional people might be
allowed three, but never more than that
the replacement statistic that is why
they quoted as 2.1 births per couple,
the 0.1 meaning you know to two would
replace the two parents and then the
point one is because of some untimely
deaths of disease or accident or
whatever, so replacement levels felt to
be just a little above two. in that
context too, he mentioned that something we
feel that we can accelerate and control
evolution, and this was in a context of
controlling who might be allowed
to reproduce. in other words, if your
genes were acceptable, you would be
allowed to bear children. but if they
were not, you might be forbidden to bear
children. that's when the the business
about sex without babies, and babies
without sex
got some development, in that certain
people who had desirable genetic
characteristics that should be
perpetuated for the good of the world,
could be / would be encouraged to
reproduce, but they need not reproduce in
the in the natural way, through sexual
intercourse, that this could be all done
in the laboratory.
then, and along those lines, is a question
which he anticipated by the way, I should
say we there was no opportunity for any
of us in the audience to ask any
questions,
but because the sexual instincts are so
strong, he said, you might think that at
first we would try to de-emphasize sex,
but that's nearly impossible to do,
because the feelings are strong, so
the plan is to go the other way, to
encourage sexual activity, to promote
sexual desire, but do it in such a way,
that it's directed away from
reproduction, and hard parcel that then
was the promotion of contraceptive
devices, they would be promoted in such a
way, that it would be just instinctive
and natural, that when you were thinking
about sex, you would automatically
connect it to contraception, that sex
without contraception would be sort of a
deliberate mental process, but most
sexual activity would be linked to
contraception. now how do you do that?
well, sex education in the schools. - and
was he talking about sex education, and
its importance back then in 1969? - oh yeah,
yeah, he developed that, to some
extent, that this would be taught in the
schools, kids would be taught to see the
the birth control pill was 69... birth
control pill came in about... - it was
around in the early 60s, was in the mid
60s. - yeah early to middle 60s, and, so this
was all fairly new stuff, and of
course he talked about things that had
been around a while,
condoms and diaphragms, but this would be
taught in the schools, the use of these. I
remember that particularly, because as he
was saying this, I was recalling some of
my teachers from high school, say "oh
I can remember Mrs. So-and-so..." you
know, she would never feel, that she
could talk about these things, of course
I was thinking of one of my algebra
teachers. - Hahaha. - He was talking about
something entirely different. But, you
know, there was a connection I made in my
mind, that in my high school, this never
would have gotten off the ground.
- Now, you were frantically taking notes
during this lecture on napkins that
you had, and so that nobody would
realize you were taking notes, because
you'd been asked not to, but you sensed
that this was important, so you were
recording this for posterity at the time.
- Yes, many of the things that he said, I
had heard before from
other sources, primarily from one source, which
I considered to be unreliable, and I had
heard it at length with some repetition,
to the point where actually it became
annoying to me, and I dismissed it,
because I considered the source not
reliable, and here it was a few years
later. See, the first I had heard it was
from this viewpoint, I stand out here
seeing over there that there's a
conspiracy going on, it's very broad
based, it's very pervasive, it's very
subtle, nobody knows it, and only a few of
us, who are able to see this, know what's
going on. Well, I dismissed that. Well
then here in 1969, I heard, from the other
end, I'm part of it, I know what's going
on, I've been told what's going on, I've
been privy to certain privileged
information, and here it is... so, you know,
hearing all this stuff from a different
perspective, I'm not an outsider looking
in, I'm an insider
speaking out the window to you, believe me,
that had quite an impact. So, that most of
the things he said I had heard before,
and then as the talk unfolded, and quite
frankly, was offensive in many ways to me,
it wasn't things that I was hearing for
the first time, but rather confirming
some things that I had heard before, like
the relocation of industries, breaking
down our armed forces, shipping our jobs
overseas, so that unemployment would go
up... those were some things, that I had heard
before, and would not believe. - but, of
course, one of the things he talked about
was, how we were going to encourage
people to buy foreign products, because
we were intentionally going to produce
shabby cars in America, so that people
would buy Japanese cars, and of course, in 1969
that most people would have thought that
was crazy talk, but what did he say along
that line, with the idea that this would
then justify the shifting of American
industries to foreign countries? - yeah,
this was to establish the global economy,
the idea be we would have one global
worldwide commercial system. It wasn't
his term, originally, but he alluded to
what they call "The Declaration of
Interdependence", I think it was
Buckminster Fuller, who wrote that, it's sort
of a parody or take-off on Thomas Jefferson's
"Declaration of Independence" for our
country, and it's been a while since I've
read that, but the opening sentences of
"The Declaration of Interdependence" are
an echo of our "Declaration of
Independence", and the idea is that, every
part of the world should be involved in
a single economy, with different parts of
the world having emphasis on different
aspects of a global economy, and the
United States was to be the "Information
Center", our smokestack industries were to
be sent to other countries. - Then did he
explain, how that would come about? - Just
that the people, who make the
decisions, the captains of industry and
politicians, would get together and
decide, "we will close a steel mill here and
reopen it there." - Now what was this about
building in obsolescence to American
cars,
so they would break down, and people would
become disillusioned with our vehicles
and buy Japanese cars? - Yes, the idea was to
promote specifically the Japanese auto
industry. This was a principle that was
applied other ways, but they they wanted
to build up the hard industries in Japan,
and not eliminate hours, but
de-emphasize them. The way to do
this was, if you bought an American built
car, and the door-handle kept coming off,
as a window cracker fell off, or some
piece under the hood, that should have
been made of metal was made of plastic
and it would crack, and he would become
irritated by that, and then your neighbor,
who had a Japanese car, would say "well
I've driven this for so many years and
so many thousands of miles, and oh I just
change the oil and the tires." - And
they actually talked about this? - Well
yeah, he said, this was in the plans.
- This was the long-range plan, as of 28
years ago, to begin orienting American
stores buying foreign products, by
intentionally creating inferior products
in America. I know, my wife was saying the
other day, that she doesn't [heech?] to buy
any clothing made in America, because
it just falls apart, you know, the threads
come out, the buttons pop off, and you
know, she attributed this just to
accidental shoddy workmanship,
but you're suggesting that maybe there
was a
plan, at least as far as certain of our
products are, to discourage Americans for
buying them, to actually buy them
overseas, thus transferring America's
wealth industry and production to other
nations, as we then lose jobs here in
America? - Right, right. I remember this
particularly, because as a matter of fact
I probably was laughing to myself, as I
do now, when I recall it. - Thinking that we
could never get away with this. - Well I
was a child during World War two, and I
remember that, we always laughed at
things that were stamped "Made in Japan".
- Right, I remember that too. - And we were
very proud, that American-made goods were
more reliable and more enduring, and so
this was a complete about-face, that
which was made in Japan now is going to
be a superior product, and ours the
inferior product, and part of the idea
behind this was a psychological
preparation, that there's sort of a
should we say patriotism, you know "things
that are made in my hometown are the
best", "things that are made in my state
are the best". - "Things that are made in
America are the best, cuz we're the best
country in the world", and they were
trying to destroy that belief? - Yes, yes, so
that you would say "well I might be a
patriotic American, but gee, I can't
afford to be buying second-rate stuff,
when I can save money buying a foreign
import." so patriotism would take a
backseat to economy, you know, to my
personal economy, and this then would
break down the kind of loyalty to your
locale or to your nation, and foster a
more cosmopolitan "citizen of the world"
attitude. - "destroy the love of country." - aha.
- okay fine, I think that's such a
fascinating insight into the mentality
of these people, who seem to have such
tremendous power over education, over
industry, or even over our ways of
reproduction, today. [We heard many] sorts of
things did they talk about, I remember one
thing that you mentioned was, how they
were going to encourage sexuality, and if
they were going to try to get people's
minds oriented under sexuality, did they
talk at all about homosexuality, and
how that would be used? - Yeah, that
would be promoted, not just merely
tolerated or permitted, but actually to be
promoted, the idea being that no child
ever results from a homosexual union. the
business of morality, especially a
religious-based morality, really would
have no part in in this future, which is
the present now. - It's almost a laugh,
because it's so ridiculous, what is
transpired, and either laugh or cry. - Well,
you know, between then and now, it's been
quite an experience to watch this unfold
right according to the script right the
unfolding nightmares with moral
foundations about once great Christian
society are progressively undermined
consider this if we're going to have
babies without sex and sex without
babies then for a large part we
interchange the section sexist there's
no real difference between men and women
now did he stress that how we were going
to feminized men and masculinize women
hey more stressed masculinizing the
women and he did feminizing the men and
this would start in youth for example
one of the things he mentioned was the
toys that were available for children
would be changed girls would get
footballs and soccer balls and baby
dolls and tea sets in a little domestic
kits like a dustpan and broom
some that would disappear entirely and
other things like that would be very
very greatly de-emphasized the know was
trying to undermine the maternal or
these rather normal instincts that women
have for being housekeepers to get them
more out into the labor market and yeah
yes exactly and certainly if they're out
in the labor market they're not going to
be having children that's right if moms
at home and she's enjoying her first and
second baby she's likely to say well
it's time for third and fourth right and
I can take care of these kids because my
hubby's making reasonable living and we
can support them and of course now you
can't you have to have the woman working
because of the tax system and because of
the actual not in dollar amount but in
purchasing about decrease in the wages
of the average American working Bale yes
yes yeah the term they use is
discretionary spending and your
discretionary spending of course you
lose all discretion because the taxable
are protected and so your you're just
trying to survive
and then if mom has one or two children
that she worries about while she's at
work
that's enough worry for her so she's not
going to say well I'm going to keep my
full-time career and have more children
you know that's just gets too much to to
be concerned about take worrying about
daycare getting somebody to take care of
the children and so what we're really
talking about is an organized plan of
social engineering laid out many many
decades ago that is coming to fruition
really in the
elevating decades mm-hmm exactly
one other thing you wanted to develop a
little bit and then we could run and
that's the about the promoting of sexual
activity through in 1969 abortion was a
crime and every one of the states and at
that time he said well it won't be long
until abortion not only is no longer a
crime that will be seen as a right and
be tack supported which at that time
sounded incredible by promoting sexual
activity among youngsters and linking it
strongly to contraception planters
realized that more pregnancies were
covered the
idea then was that's okay if there are
more pregnancies that occur we'll have
an abortion back up and people who would
otherwise oppose abortion will change
their mind when they say well this is my
daughter who's pregnant
young and tender age and portion
restrictions might be okay for everybody
else so you were saying how they were
going to change our attitude towards
abortion and how in night Department in
1969 abortion was illegal in every state
so what did they plan how are we going
to change that well the idea is to
promote early sexual activity among the
kids connecting it strongly with the use
of contraceptives they would be taught
that the two just naturally should go
together
and with the realization that was more
sexual activity there would be more
pregnancies more contraceptive failures
one might say but no need to worry about
cluttering up the planet with unwanted
babies because abortion then would be
available as a backup and with young
girls getting pregnant too early in
their life people who otherwise would
maybe object to abortion when you know
if it was in somebody else's life would
say video but I no longer Jack because
this is my daughter and I don't want her
to have to carry this pregnancy to term
because she's not yet mature enough to
to be a mother and take care of a baby
so it was sort of a win-win situation
for them it would break down resistance
to abortion as well as reinforcing
continually the need for contraception
or sex without babies you know as you
talk about this it sounds so diabolical
almost like the plant had come right out
of the pit of hell yes
I think so and start looking back on
this as you've seen this unfolding over
the last 29 years or 28 years it must
have been terribly terribly frustrating
for you seeing these things and knowing
what was going on and yet realizing that
the vast majority of the American people
had no idea at all what was transpiring
what was frustrating and even talking
with some of my colleagues who heard the
same presentation
not very long afterwards they had all
seem to forget it they'd say oh yeah I
remember he was here I remember he
talked about some stuff but as far as
details and saying well don't you
remember when he said this that and the
other that's enough
did he say that well I don't know like
when I say that what comes to mind is
one of my colleagues so dr. day had
spoken about the demise pill the demise
pill there there was consideration to be
given to an arbitrary age after which
you know everybody should just pass on
the age could be set by law 75 80 85
whatever seemed to be appropriate at the
time and then when you reach that age he
would be a candidate to take the demise
pill and he said this attitudes about
death needed to be changed and made more
quote realistic so you know we're all
headed for death one way or another so
why not do this in a very cerebral
scientific kind of way so the idea was
that when you had reached the legal age
you could have this nice banquet sort of
a farewell banquet with your family and
friends and afterwards go out and take
your demise pill and sleep away
peacefully oh one of my colleagues who
have we were
outside a meeting in the hospital and
there was some talk about he was having
some pain he was coming into the
hospital a ticket some tests and maybe
have some surgery acceptable hey Fred
what he closed - and might you know the
night before the operation maybe you're
a little restless and you can't sleep
and the nurse comes in and says well
here's your sleeping pill are you going
to take it if you take it maybe they'll
have to do the operation okay he just
left they he said did he say that I
didn't remember them I said yeah you
better remember he said it and so they
were even back in 1969 they were talking
about a more or less coerced or forced a
euthanasia did they talk at all about
other countries how they were going to
control population in other countries or
pause the possibility of fomenting
disease to control a population yes
there were there were a couple of things
there one there was a part of the
presentation where he said new diseases
will appear they will be very difficult
to diagnose doctor seeing these for the
first time of course will not know
what's going on and the reason I
remember this so strongly was I was
fairly new in practice and after hearing
him talk about new diseases that would
appear I'd have a youngster in the
office and be examining him and I you
know say - he's got disappear in these
symptoms and it just doesn't add up it
wasn't you know absolutely certain what
was going on well right away my memory
would ring a bell and say could this be
one of those new diseases he was talking
about well it turned out that that was
medication in my practice or with any of
my kids but in in retrospect I think he
was talking about AIDS
there were some other things that were
said that sort of lead me to that
instruction what other things rather
because of course my nature interest has
been the AIDS epidemic I've been
battling this for over a decade so one
of the things were there that if you can
recall it I know this is a long time ago
but I just think the Lord that you took
those notes and on the on the napkins
and then we recorded them what other
things did he say that made makes you
thinks that perhaps the AIDS epidemic
has something to do with it with a plan
the continent of Africa is a very rich
continent now that's what he said well
I'm sort of parallel lines right and I
don't recall that this was the in
immediate juxtaposition to AIDS but it
was pretty close okay so of course the
the AIDS epidemic is simply decimating
depopulating Africa the American people
don't know that but it's really
happening today and so was he talking
about possible disease Africa or just
the fact that it was such a rich rich
continent well here we have a world
that's soon to be overpopulated soon to
run out of natural resources and here's
this great big continent of Africa full
of resources
now this continent should not be left to
people who have never been able to
develop it
the continent should be under the
control of people who know how to
develop and manage all these resources
and in effect but what that means is you
have to get rid of the people that are
there now
not totally perhaps but in large part to
make room for the managers to move in
that's a frightening frightening thing
to contemplate and yet that's exactly
what is happening in Africa today and
the the interesting thing is that it's
always filled under concern love and
we're helping you out you know we love
all our fellow men but there were some
comments about let's face it not all
people are equal we all know that some
people are not as smart not as capable
and capable of doing the only menial
tasks and there were some racial
illusions there now if you have a
continent full of people that are not
capable of doing what Europeans are
capable of doing or Europeans who have
become Americans are capable of doing
and then you can't leave such a large
rich continent under the control of
people that can't manage it the ultimate
in racism just hiding behind the the
banner of love and compassion yes yes
yes okay fine so basically he was
talking about the DC of these diseases
would be produced where they come from
these new diseases that were going to
come into society that was not explicit
at the time as I recall it I just the
best I can recall was it they would
occur that I kept wondering am I going
to miss them will I ever recognize them
or even will I get them right you know
what I myself succumbed
- something like that but in terms of
how this would be brought about I don't
think that was addressed at all okay so
we begin to see though an active program
that not just sort of passively bringing
about population control but actively
bringing about population control yeah
were there any other points that he made
as far as population control is
concerned but you know because these
ideas is so foreign to the average
listener the idea that we would have a
demise pill in other words we would kill
older people and now we would 1969 the
idea that we would start aborting the
children of this country in mass numbers
was was so foreign
did he talk at all about pushing
abortion towards certain racial or
ethnic groups that sort of grew out of
talking about promoting drug use well
let's get into talking about promoting
drug use because that is so important
especially today when we see drugs
destroying the inner cities of America
not everybody deserves space on the
planet not everybody deserves the right
to marry and reproduce so certain people
have to be sort of haunted and I don't
mean individual selection where you
identify a particularly human being but
certain populations with certain group
characteristics have to be shunted now
part of this grows out of transferring
industry overseas if I thought in terms
of our steel industry where a lot of
wage earners you know didn't have to
have a lot of education a lot of savvy
to do the work and earn a wage and raise
a family but when these
industries are either closed or
transferred then the wage earners don't
have any other any place to go to earn
money to raise family women this was an
education guy I heard I learned a whole
lot there he said women are attracted to
men who are good providers see when I
was a kid they I thought they were
attracted to Clark Gable and
good-looking movie star and so this was
a really revelation of my age at that
time kids as women are attracted to men
who are good providers they don't much
care what a man looks like whereas men
are more attracted to woman by her
appearance and also a man identifies
himself by his work and as I thought
about what he said many times in five
years I think that's absolutely correct
I'm Joe Blow I'm a welder I'm John Jones
I'm a stockbroker you know I think it's
true we do tend to identify or socially
well if you have no job by which to
identify yourself you're not a good
provider
to attract a woman to become your wife
then you're not going to have as great
an opportunity to bear children now if
you have a whole bunch of young men who
are unemployed are not good providers
you have no strong identity through
their work you know what these guys do
when they get together well there's a
certain homosexual promotion there and a
certain you know falling into crime sure
which
now a consequence in which was
recognized well know by what you're
talking about crime what are you talking
about drug use other learners drug use
put in to come into this whole situation
okay now if you're young and you have no
job you have no family no
responsibilities and life is just a bore
and you're more vulnerable to abusing
drugs no did he suggest that they would
encourage drug use yeah yeah that is an
incredible incredible prediction of what
the direction that these people that dr.
day represented would be taking our
society because they had to have
powerful control a powerful influence
over governmental positions and
governmental activities the idea was to
create sort of neighborhoods doesn't
seem like the right word anymore but
certain areas of the cities that would
be the jungle we have progressed so far
that their laws of natural selection no
longer operate this is sort of a near
quote paraphrasing there is natural
population control in previous years
predatory animals and Wars and disease
and such but now the technology has
nullified a lot of that this is part of
overpopulation so since the former law
of the jungle no longer applies we would
now have a new law of the jungle and the
jungle would be certain areas in
primarily large metropolitan areas where
people just have no opportunity no hope
the areas would be allowed to
deteriorate
with the idea that as the spirit grew
and people sought refuge in drugs and
alcohol then a certain amount of
violence would be predictable and that's
okay because that would you know if you
died in 1969 because somebody shot you
or if you died in 1769 because a bear
got you a model and got you what's the
difference you're dead in either case
you succumb to the law of the jungle the
survival of the fittest on the other
hand means that in a time when you had
to be a crack shot with your musket and
you got the mountain lion the only
difference is in now instead of being
musketeer now you're computer genius
those are the criteria by which
Selectric survives and now of course
when dr. Dave was making all these
predictions and telling you what the
future held didn't he make some
reference to the fact that everything
was in place but nothing would stop this
at the present time and so he felt at
least somewhat able to reveal these
things to you yes yes that was very
early in the presentation that was said
that was 69 and as Beth I can recall
there there is no nothing specified is
exactly what was in place now that
hadn't been and he said something that
even as recently as five or ten years
earlier he could not have spoken with
such assurance about what the future
held and of course he went on then to
become some sort of an official or
planned parenthood he was at the time
when he spoke he he was medical director
of Planned Parenthood Federation of
America and he had been a professor at
the year medical school and he was
very well-known neonatologist yes yes
and then he left here and went to
Planned Parenthood Federation in New
York became disillusioned there and I'm
not sure the nature that disillusionment
whether it was ideologic or what but he
did become disillusioned with them and
left and he seen his subsequently died
he's passed away yeah yeah he died mmm
Peter roughly eight years ago I'd have
to look to see you as well
so he never saw his dream come to
fruition but certainly the people who
are and in sympathy with these ideas are
seeing it unfold today is America moves
into chaos and crime and drugs and new
diseases developing all across America
so basically as you look back on this
what do you think possibly motivated
that dr. day to tell you these
incredible things everybody asked that
question and I can only speculate they I
really don't know there was not an
opportunity to ask but they I think
there were a couple of things that were
involved one was that I think he had
divided feelings about this on the one
hand repeatedly saying this is the only
way there's no other alternative feeling
that some or another the human race
would perish otherwise and that the
human race should be provided to go on
well this this is a very common position
taken by elitist professor Quigley who
we have studied very extensively Bill
Clinton's mentor I really believe that
we needed a ruling elite as Western
civilization would be destroyed and what
you're really describing is a ruling
elite with a program to try to preserve
at least some element of civilization
yes yes I think that's the the upfront
part of it and then in the intervening
years it has often occurred to me that
what also seems to underline this is a
more long-range look you know they talk
about progress of the human race we're
progressing and one should stop and say
well progressing toward what right and
especially when you hear somebody say we
believe now that we have the means to
accelerate and control evolution
evolution toward what well I think one
possibility I don't know that I've heard
anybody state this explicitly is that we
will progress toward becoming gods that
sounds a little bizarre but when you go
back to Regenesis and they Adam and Eve
took from the tree of knowledge and the
serpent said ye shall be as gods in
other words what you're suggesting is
what energizes these people is a
spiritual force the idea that the
Serpent's message that ye should be as
gods if if you go along with my program
mm-hmm you can't evolve to a higher
plane and as incredible as it may seem I
read many many publications by people
these are a Celtic and Luciferian
publications where this is the basic
underlying theme for mankind will
supplant God and bring utopia to the
world well well I'm thinking about the
book of Genesis when you go to the end
of that chapter and when God expelled
Adam and Eve and he said they they go to
the tree of knowledge verse or two later
he sets a cherubim in guard of the Tree
of Life
and I think about that you know we get
all this sperm banks and cloning of
animals talking about cross species
fertilization I often think about that
you know babies without sex and sex
without babies and early to be very
early in the game God set up a chair be
said they go to the tree of knowledge
I'm going to keep them away from the
tree of life just for fun go to Genesis
and read that and and see whether you
find any application to what's going on
today well I think that this this is all
prophetic I mean we see these things
unfolding and and for people who don't
understand order know the Bible these
things seem impossible for those of us
and I know you're a believer who CV
Singh son further we see God's hand and
we also see that the hand of the Lucifer
in this whole incredible story well
other any other points you'd like to
bring out for our listeners well we were
talking earlier about unisex stuff or at
least I think we alluded to it the
masculinization of women girls and I
don't know whether you've noticed in
your area but in our area in the last
few years the sports pages are full of
girls sports now the girls basketball
you know and as if that true out here
well yeah sure and we have a girls
basketball teams the other you know
Olympic girls basketball teams girls
volleyball teams all of these things you
know where they're so competitive as men
mm-hmm soccer big thing out there no we
don't have soccer out here to my
knowledge it'll probably be coming
women's soccer you speaking up well know
women's and man okay bye probably Sunday
co-educational so I don't know but
the reason for this is that we can't
have girls and lacy dresses smelling
perfumey and attracting the men even if
they're sweaty there nothing was
attractive right right incredible
incredible did he actually talk about
things of this sort oh yeah that was
very explicit girls would would be made
less attractive because they would be
just as you said sweating right full of
you know sports and just like another
guy rising big muscles and all those
things so that was the one of the early
parts of masculinizing women and then of
course another part that I don't think
he put in these terms by interpreting
these terms then his a woman is a good
woman
to the extent that she mimics a man and
that is leaving her home and you know
going out into the workforce and
becoming CEO or office manager some big
outfit real estate I'm taking care of
children but along with with the D Eman
izing of girls in the professional
magazines that I get where drug products
are advertised there's a one that shows
all these girls in their soccer uniforms
mud all over them their hair is all wet
and stringy and this is held out to the
young girls is you know this is what you
ought to be this is what a I think young
girl is she's a muddy soccer player I
said because you know we can do anything
the boys can do and we can do it better
and the competition between women and
then without realizing that we all have
a placed and a part to play in in God's
plan well I doctor denigan has been a
fascinating fascinating hour we'll be
playing this this afternoon in several
times on our various radio programs I
want to thank you so very very much for
taking time from your busy schedule to
be here on Radio Liberty because I think
your message going along with many of
the other messages that we have begins
to tie this together
and I hope our listeners will be far
wiser from having heard now your
memories from the lecture by dr. de 1969
28 years ago what's been a pleasure to
be on and I hope it's helpful to folks I
hope it will be to may God bless you and
I have a baby at some time in the future
we can come talk to you again well I
would like bye-bye thanks a lot bye-bye
bye
okay well this is dr. Stan an amazing
amazing take a tape with the gentleman
who I believe that God has preserved him
to tell us the story and I hope you've
enjoyed this program as much as we've
enjoyed bringing it to you and so until
next time dr. Stan goodbye and may the
Lord be with you
Oh